Guide to the Tim Dlugos Papers MSS.087
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries B: Correspondence from Tim Dlugos
    - Correspondence from Tim Dlugos: Haines -- Richman:, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Haines, Rev. Denise; Helminiak, Rev. Daniel; Hunter College -- Department of English; Kavanagh, Aidan; Kikel, Rudy; Kocharhook, Ken; Lally, Michael; Lambert, Arthur; Maxwell, Anne; Maxwell, [ ]; McKinley, Scott; McManus, Harry; Meyers, Richard; Miner, Rev. Jerald; Moore, Rev. Paul; Parisi, [ ]; Quinn, Alice; Richman, Robert
    - Correspondence from Tim Dlugos: Schmidt -- Z and Unknown Last Names:, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Schmidt, Andy; Sherover, Charles; Sikov, Ed; [Snyder], Rob; Society for the Increase of the Ministry; Spring, Helen; Storace, Patricia; Strub, Sean; Sullivan, Bishop Walter F.; Sussler, Betsy; Trinidad, David; Tyson, Rae; Wells, Rev.; Last name unknown: Chris; Marty; Peter and Brian; Kenward; Theophilus.
    - Correspondence -- business, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Subseries C: Correspondence to and from the estate of Tim Dlugos
    Correspondence to and from the Estate of Tim Dlugos
    - Correspondence to and from the Estate of Tim Dlugos, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Book projects
    Book projects
    - Entre Nous -- MS/TS 1981, 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Entre Nous -- production folder, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - A Fast Life -- early drafts, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - A Fast Life -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - A Fast Life -- TS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - A Fast Life -- Gallies for O Press 1978, 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - For Years -- TS fragments and Jawbone Press photocopy, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - G-9 -- MS/TS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - High There -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Je Suis Ein Americano -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Living (photocopy), undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Notes on Proust (photocopy), undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Outlines for Three Works -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Outlines for Three Works -- TS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Outlines for Three Works (photocopy), undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Powerless (Original) -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Powerless (Original) -- MS/TS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Powerless (Original) -- MS/TS with notes, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Powerless (Original) -- TS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Powerless -- production Folder, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Powerless -- production copy (complete), undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Some Poems -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Strong Place (Private Printing) -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Strong Place (Private Printing) -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Strong Place (Private Printing) -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Strong Place (Private Printing) -- MS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Strong Place (Private Printing) -- unbound and bound copies, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Strong Place -- MS/TS, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Strong Place -- production folder, undated; 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Subseries B: Poetry manuscripts
    Poetry manuscripts
    - Poetry manuscripts -- through 1971, 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1972, 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1973, 31142040616461 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Unfinished poetry manuscripts -- early 1970's, 1970-1975; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1974, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1975, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Unfinished poetry manuscripts -- mid 1970's, 1970-1975; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1976, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1977, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1978, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1979, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1980, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1981, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1982, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1983, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Unfinished poetry manuscripts -- early 1980's, 1980-1985; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1984, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1986, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1987, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1988, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1989, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Unfinished poetry manuscripts -- late 1980's and 1990, 1985-1990; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Poetry manuscripts -- 1990, 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous poems by Tim Dlugos, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Poems -- Canner St.(computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Poems -- Roosevelt Hospital (computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Poems -- Rowe St.(computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Poems -- West 47th Street (computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Poems -- West 83rd Street (computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Poems -- c/o Chris Wiss (computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Poems -- miscellaneous (computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Poems -- miscellaneous (computer disks), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Subseries C: Other manuscripts by Tim Dlugos
    Other manuscripts by Tim Dlugos
    - Animus, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Beyond the New Wave: An Exhibition of Representational Paintings -- introduction by Tim Dlugos, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Cayo Hueso: A Novel, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - The Christian Lover, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - The Future of Gay Publishing, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Pathic, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Police Dog, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Preserves -- a play with Bernard Welt, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - The President's Son: A Novel, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Remembering Larry (Stanton), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - The Spirit That Moves Us: Profile of Arthur A.Schomburg, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Waffles: A Short Story, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Miscellaneous writing fragments, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Manuscripts (possibly) by Tim Dlugos, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Subseries D: Interviews conducted by Tim Dlugos
    Interviews conducted by Tim Dlugos
    - Brainard, Joe -- interview, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - DeLynn, Jane -- interview, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Divine -- interview, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Lally, Michael -- interview, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Subseries E: Manuscripts by others
    Manuscripts by others
    - Other People's Poems [submitted and printed in Lucy & Ethel Magazine or Some of Us Press]; Carrick, Laban; Cox, Ed -- see correspondence (folder 2); Everhard, Jim -- see correspondence (folder 2); Fraer, Peter; Frankel, Danny; Feinberg, Larry; Genson, Neil L.; Gilhol___], Patricia; Hamilton, Steve; Henry, Gerrit; Joselow, Beth; Lally, Michael; Maxwell, Anne; Notley, Alice; Trinidad, David; Winch, Terence; Uknown names; (see also series 4, subseries E folder 184), undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Other people's manuscripts; Berg, Christopher; Hannah, Duncan; Pei, Shynn-Yien; Raskas, Jonathan; Strong, Johnathan; Unknown names, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Dennis Cooper Manuscripts: A Herd -- TS; My Mark -- MS/TS; The Tenderness of the Wolves -- MS/TS, undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Articles by and about Dennis Cooper., undated; 31142040616479 (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Series III: Biographical Information
  - Subseries A: General biographical material
    General biographical material
    - Working bibliography of Tim Dlugos poems prepared by David Trinidad, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Biographical information, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Cory, Jim."Tim Dlugos: 1950-1990." The James White Review.10:2 (Winter 1993).18-19., 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - DeLynn, Jane."Francis Timothy Dlugos." Outweek.79/ 80.(Jan 9, 1991) 36, 90., 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - In Memoriam: Tim Dlugos 1950-1990. Poetry Project Newsletter.141 (April/May 1990).10-12., 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Remembering Tim. Washington Review.16:6 (April/May 1991).3-18., 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Journal and poetry -- 1973, 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Diaries -- 1976, 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Desk calendar -- 1986, 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Aids Journal -- 1989, 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Jack Sheer photographs, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Party invitations, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - La Salle College -- Christian Brotherhood, poetry workshops, and miscellaneous material, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Hunter College -- course work, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Miscellaneous material, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Miscellaneous periodicals and clippings, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Subseries B: Yale Divinity School
    Yale Divinity School
    - Yale Divinity School -- reflective, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Yale Divinity School -- reflective, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Yale Divinity School -- reflective, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Yale Divinity School -- work, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Yale Divinity School -- work, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Yale Divinity School -- work, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Subseries C: Fundraising
    Fundraising
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Fundraising, undated; 31142040616487 (Box 3, Folder 122)
- Series IV: Readings, Reviews, Periodical Contributions
  - Subseries A: Readings and press information
    Readings and press information [see also oversize].
    - Readings of Tim Dlugos, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Beyond Baroque Center readings (see also series 4, subseries E folder 188) (see also Oversize folder 197), undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Little Caesar Press (see also Oversize folder 198), undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Some of Us Press, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Other people's readings(see also Oversize folder 199), undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - Subseries B: Interviews and reviews on Tim Dlugos
    Interviews and reviews on Tim Dlugos
    - Blade Magazine's interview with Tim Dlugos, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Published reviews of Tim Dlugos' books; Abbott, Steve."In the Spirit of Rimbaud." [ ].(Aug.24, 1979).15, [ ].; Beaudouin, David."Tim Dlugos, an Appreciation." Washington Review.(Dec.1982 -- Jan 1983).28.; Funsten, Kenneth."Entre Nous: New Poems." Los Angeles Times.(Oct.10, 1982).[ ].; Griffith, Patricia."None of the Above, New Poets of the USA" Washington Review.[( )].[ ].; Kikel, Rudy."Entre Nous Le Deluge." New York Native.(Dec.20, 1982 -- Jan.2, 1983).41.; Lerner, Eric."Dlugos' Songs." Washington Blade.13:22 (Oct, 1979-1983; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Subseries C: Blurbs and interviews by Tim Dlugos
    Blurbs and reviews by Tim Dlugos
    - Blurbs: Gerstler, Amy; Huston, Bo, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Auchincloss, Louis.The Rector of Justin.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Burroughs, William S.Cities of the Red Night.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Drury, Allen.Advise and Consent.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Perloff, Marjorie.Frank O'Hara: Poet Among Painters.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Rorem, Ned.The Nantucket Diary.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Sanford, David.Me & Ralph.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Violi, Paul.Splurge.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Windam, Donald.Tennessee William's Letters to Donald Windam, 1940-1965 and Tanaquil.-review (see also series 4, subseries E, folder 183), undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Windam, Donald.Two People.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Weiner, Hannah.Little Books/Indians.-- review, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Subseries D: Contributions to anthologies and magazines
    Contributions to anthologies and magazines
    - The Certitude of Night, "Harding's Beach." American Letters and Commentary.2 (Fall 1989).78-80., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Night Life, Famous Writers," "Day Light." Angels of the Lyre: A Gay Poetry Anthology.Ed.Winston Leyland.San Francisco: Parjandrum Press, 1975.49-50., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - All Soul's Day, "As Alive,""Signs of Madness." Art and Understanding.1: 1 (Fall 1991) 5-6; "Erosion." Art and Understanding.1: 13 (Spring 1992) 13., 1991, 1992; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Bill Sullivan. Arts Magazine.58:5 (Jan.1984)0.115.-- profile, 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - The Steve Hamilton Sestina. B City.8 (1993) 24-5., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Green Acres. Barney: The Modern Stone Age Magazine.4 (Spring 1984).13., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Healing the World from Battery Park. The Best American Poetry 1993.Eds.Louis Gld David Lehman.New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1993.58-61., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - As It Is, "American Baseball," "Sounding Back," "Great Books of the 1950's," "John Tongue," "Another Stanza for Martina." Black Box.8 (n.d.) side b.[sound recording], undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Harmony in Red, "Ordinary Time," "Radiant Child." Bomb.35 (Spring 1991).93., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - West 22nd Street. Brooklyn Review.6 (1989)0.46."Powerless." Brooklyn Review.7 (1990).1-3; "Good Morning." Brooklyn Review.8 (1991) 2; "Psalm," "Spinner." Brooklyn Review.9 (1992) 29-30., 1989-1992; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Signs of Madness. Chemical Imbalance Magazine.2:3 (n.d.).75., undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - You are There, "Day for Paul," "At the Point," "Bindo Altoviti," "In London," "Great Art." Coming Attractions: An Anthology of American Poets in Their Twenties.Ed.Dennis Cooper.L.A.: Little Caesar Press, 1980.35-42., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Powerless. Day of Hope.1 (n.d.).32., undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - D.O.A. Editor's Choice III: Fiction, Poetry & Art from the U.S.Small Press (1984-1990): Selections from Nominations Made by the Editors of Independent, Noncommercial Literary Presses and Magazines, of Work Published in Them from 1984 to 1990.Eds.Morton Sklar and Mary Biggs.New York: Spirit that Moves Us Press, 1991.101-3., 1984-1991; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - The Legend of Gaucho. The Faber Book of Movie Verse.Ed.Philip French.London: Faber and Faber, 1993.394-5., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - White Petals. Four Petals.27:4 (Summer 1978).[ ]., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - New Music. Gandhabba.1:1 (Jan 1984) 29., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Poem After Dinner, "Flaming Angel." Hanging Loose.23 (Summer 1974).9-10; "The Nineteenth Century is 183 Years Old," "Lit," "Summer, South Brooklyn," "Healing the World from Battery Park." Hanging Loose.60 (1992) 16-21., 1974-1992; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Signs of Madness, "D.O.A." Jugular Defenses: An Aids Anthology.London: The Oscars Press, 1994.74-5,106-7., 1996-1997; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Parachute. Long Shot.10 (n.d.) 63-5., undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Desire Under the Pines, "From Journal," "Solidarity." Mag City.13 (1982).15-18., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Stanza for Martina, Stanza for Martina," "Stanza for Martina," "Chapter Two." Mass Transit.5 (Fall 1974).2-3., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Naked Brunch. New York Native.1 (Dec.5-18, 1980).33: (Dec.29 -- Jan.8, 1980)0.31.& other MS, 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Summer Wishes... New York Native.(June 4-17, 1984).37-8., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Where I Hang My Cassock. New York Native.(Oct.5 -- Nov.18, 1984).43-4., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Gilligan's Island, "President Truman," "American Baseball," "Mallarm" None of the Above: New Poet's of the U.S.A.New York: Crossings Press, 1976.187-92., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Retrovir. Outweek.11 (Sept 4, 1989) 55; "D.O.A." Outweek.66 (Oct.3, 1990).56; "Turnadot." Outweek.79/ 80 (Jan 9, 1991) 72.(see series 3, subseries A folder ), 1989-1991; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Untitled, "July." Paris Review.29:102 (Spring 1987).211-212; "G-9." Paris Review.32:115 (Summer 1990).244-260., 1987-1990; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Poppers. Personal Injury Magazine.2 (Jan., 1979).22., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Retrovir. Poets for Life: Seventy-Six Poets Respond to Aids.New York: Persea Books, 1989.65., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - The Morning, "All Soul's Day," "Station." Santa Monica Review.4:2 (Spring 1992) 98-101., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Steve Reich and Musicians, "Film." Shiny International.[2] [( )].[ ]."Fan Mail From Some Flounder." Shiny International.4 [( )].[ ]."Turnadot," "Etiquette in 1969," "Friends Service." Shiny International.6 (1991) 53-6., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - New Hope, "Daylight," "Close," "Desire Under the Pines." The Son of the Male Muse: New Gay Poetry.Ed.Ian Young.New York: Trumansburg: Crossing Press, 1993.82-6., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - The Black Forest, "Ten Movies." The Thursday Book: Selected Poetry from the Dove Readings.Ed.J.Wesley Clark.Anapolis: Dove Books, 1975.11-12., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Chibbaro, Lou and Keen, Lisa M."Fighting Back: Gay Communities Respond to the Aids health Crisis." Washington Blade.14:5 (Feb.4, 1983) [ ],32-3.(Tim Dlugos quoted on p.33)., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Some Memories of Mass Transit.Washington Review.14:2 (Aug./Sept.1988)0.24.& MS, 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Octavian, "A Sense." The World.42 (Jan 1992) 51-3."Goodbye to Chrysis," "Awash in Angels." The World.51 (1995) 40-3., 1992-1995; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Qum. A Year in Poetry: A Treasury of Classic and Modern Verses for Every Date on the Calendar.New York: Crown Publishers, [ ].16., undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - American Baseball, "President Truman," "Gilligan's Island," "Note to J.A.," "Mallarm ZZZ.(1974) 44-51., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - At the Point, "Day for Paul," "You are There," "Poles Apart." ZZZZZ.(1977) 138-42., 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - Subseries E: Periodicals edited or published by Tim Dlugos
    Periodicals edited or published by Tim Dlugos
    - Christopher Street Magazine;"Rough Trade" -- PR release; "Rough Trade" -- Dec.1976.- MS; "Rough Trade" -- Apr.1977.- MS; "Rough Trade" -- Nov0.1977.- MS; "Christopher Street Guide to New York" - outline; Christopher Street Magazine.2:2 (Aug.1977); Christopher Street Magazine.3:3 (Oct.1978); Christopher Street Magazine.6:12 (Jan.1983); Christopher Street Magazine.7:3 (Apr.1983)., 1976-1983; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Lucy & Ethel Magazine; (see also series 2, subseries E folder 89), undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Poetry Project Newsletter: Layout notes: Fundraising for the poetry project; Poetry Project Newsletter.70 (Dec.1979).; Poetry Project Newsletter.108 (Oct.1984).; Poetry Project Newsletter.109 (Nov.1984).; Poetry Project Newsletter.110 (Dec.1984).; Poetry Project Newsletter.111 (Jan./Feb.1985).; Poetry Project Newsletter.112 (Mar.1985).; Poetry Project Newsletter0.113.(Apr.1985).; Poetry Project Newsletter.114 (May 1985).; 186.The Public Citizen, 1979-1985; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Tim Magazine, undated; 31142040616495 (Box 4, Folder 187)
- Series V: Video, Audio, and Electronic Files
  Series contains all media for the Tim Dlugos Papers.
  - Subseries A: Video Recordings - Access Copies
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
    - Tim Dlugos Memorial Reading -- (Dec.30, 1990) (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 087.0006)
      General note
      Format: DVD
      Duration: 01:08:40
      Original Format: VHS
    - Good Morning America (Tim Dlugos appearance) (Oct.31, 1990) (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 087.0007)
      Duration: 00:05:00
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    - Tim Dlugos Memorial Reading -- (Dec.30, 1990) (Box 5, Folder 087.0002A)
      Format: VHS
    - Good Morning America (Tim Dlugos appearance) (Oct.31, 1990) (Box 5, Folder ID: 087.0001)
  - Subseries C: Audio Recordings - Access Copies
    - Tim Dlugos at Beyond Baroque / May 11, 1984, ID: 087.0009 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 087.0009)
      Format: CD
      Duration: 00:45:00
      Original Format: Audio Cassette
    - Dennis Cooper at Beyond Baroque / May 11, 1984, ID: 087.0011 (Box Shared Fales 124, Cd 087.0011)
  - Subseries D: Audio Recordings - Originals
    - Tim Dlugos and Dennis Cooper Reading -- Beyond Baroque (May 11, 1984) [see also series 4, subseries A, folder 124] (Box 5, Folder ID: 087.0003)
      Format: Audio Cassette
      Duration: [Unknown]
    - 7 Out Write Conference: Poetry and Writing, Undated (Box 5, Folder ID: 087.0004)
  - Subseries E: Electronic Files
    The computer disks transferred from Tim's computer have all been printed and interfiled into the appropriate series and folders.
    Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
    - Computer Files, Undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
      Format: N/A
- Series VI: Realia
  - Assorted realia, undated (Box 5, Folder 193)